finditclassifieds.com 2018-01-26

# Find It Classifieds | Privacy Policy

Updated **09/04/2017**

 **Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Third Party Advertisers
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the finditclassifieds.com website. On some pages, you can submit advertisements, make ad inquiries and register to edit ads. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an ad only to sell your item or service. We do not share this information with outside parties except to advertise your ad on our site. 

It is our general governing principal is not to retain unnecessary data. As a result, our policies dictate that stale accounts older than 360 days and advertisements beyond 90 days be automatically deleted to reduce our data storage requirements unless requested law enforcement. Simply put, we are low budget and don't care to retain your ad old data because that gets expensive and don't and we don't share it.

You can register with our website if you would like to have the ability to modify or mark ads as sold. Information you submit on our website will not store passed the expiration date of your ad unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Third Party Advertisers:**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain it by logging in to your account . We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at [phone number] or send us an email at [info@finditclassifieds.com](mailto:info@finditclassifieds.com). 

FinditClassifieds.com, your [free alternative to Craigslist](http://craigslist.org/)   
Copyright © 1997-2018 WebzCom E-Business Services. All rights reserved.
